{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Granite Restoration Companies","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"__cache./api/resource/task/62560/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":62560,"taskName":"Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing","taskDescription":"Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing","xmTaskDescriptor":"Granite Restoration Companies","matchable":false,"profileable":false,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":null,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"stone restoration polishing polish natural granite","textMessagingName":"Granite polishing","rolloverLongDesc":"Polishing \u0026 restoring dull granite \u0026 granite tile and flooring","rolloverShortDesc":"Includes granite tile polishing","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Polish or Restore Granite floors, tile, and countertops. HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened contractors in your area.","htmlTitle":"Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing Companies \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Granite Floors, Tile, Countertops","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":74,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":5,"bridgeTaskOid":0,"bridgeTaskText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkText":null,"bridgeTaskLinkId":0,"bridgeTaskActive":"N","xmName":"Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Granite Restoration Project","urlName":"Granite-Restoration-Polishing","taskConsiderationId":2,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Granite Restoration \u0026 Polishing Companies in \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Floors, Tile, Countertops","searchKeywords":"stone restoration polishing polish natural granite","emcCategoryOid":-12073,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":9211,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","__cache./api/resource/task/interview/62560/":{"taskOID":62560,"originalTaskOID":62560,"setID":9211,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":500023,"questionDisplayText":"Stone Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the stone located? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Stone Location","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","answerDisplayText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":500023,"questionDisplayText":"Stone Location","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Where is the stone located? (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"Stone Location","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","answerDisplayText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":2528,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Floor","answerDisplayText":"Floor","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6529,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","answerDisplayText":"Tub / shower or surrounding area","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4483,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Outdoors","answerDisplayText":"Outdoors","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3412,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Kitchen","answerDisplayText":"Kitchen","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1662,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Countertop","answerDisplayText":"Countertop","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6736,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Wall","answerDisplayText":"Wall","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":983,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Bathroom","answerDisplayText":"Bathroom","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":930,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Backsplash","answerDisplayText":"Backsplash","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"semThreeIcons":false,"isCookielessUser":true}